<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dinosaurs</string>
    <string name="app_title">Armored Dinosaurs List</string>
    <string name="ankylosaurus">Ankylosaurus</string>
    <string name="ankylosaurus_info">Ankylosaurus was a slow moving herbivore
        and needed protection from these hungry hunters. This protection came in the form of sharp
        spikes, and a long heavy hammer tail that could be used to break the legs of its enemies.
        Even the eyelids of Ankylosaurus were plated for protection. Ankylosaurus was nearly 2.5
        meters (8ft) wide and 10 meters (33ft) long. Yet it only stood about 1-2 meters (3-6.5ft)
        off the ground.</string>
    <string name="edmontonia">Edmontonia</string>
    <string name="edmontonia_info">Edmontonia was one of the last armored dinosaurs to thrive during
        the Cretaceous Period. It was also one of the largest armored dinosaurs, standing at over 7
        meters in length, or 23 feet. This huge dinosaur had massive and powerful legs to support
        its weight, and was covered in long sharp horns, making it a dangerous adversary. </string>
    <string name="euoplocephalus">Euoplocephalus</string>
    <string name="euoplocephalus_info">Euoplocephalus was one of the most common dinosaurs to live
        in North America around 70 million years ago. Because they were so plentiful, their fossils
        have been found in a number of locations. These fossils show that Euoplocephalus was well
        protected. Even its eyelids had bony protrusions protecting the eyes. Euoplocephalus had
        spikes or horns on the side of its head and also running down its armored back. </string>
    <string name="hylaeosaurus">Hylaeosaurus</string>
    <string name="hylaeosaurus_info">Hylaeosaurus comes from a fossil discovered in southern England.
        This fossil is still embedded in solid rock, and as a result is difficult to piece together.
        As a result, much of what we believe about Hylaeosaurus is actually borrowed from its close
        relatives such as Polacanthus. </string>
    <string name="minmi">Minmi</string>
    <string name="minmi_info">One of the first armored dinosaurs to evolve, Minmi was discovered in
        Australia. During the Cretaceous period, Australia was actually further south than it is today.
        This early armored dinosaur was only about 3 meters long, or about 10 feet. Minmi had a sharp
        beak and a large flat tooth it could use for grinding its food, which consisted primarily of
        plants. Minmi was covered with small spikes which were used for protection. </string>
    <string-array name="dinoList">
        <item>@string/ankylosaurus</item>
        <item>@string/edmontonia</item>
        <item>@string/euoplocephalus</item>
        <item>@string/hylaeosaurus</item>
        <item>@string/minmi</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dinoInfoList">
        <item>@string/ankylosaurus_info</item>
        <item>@string/edmontonia_info</item>
        <item>@string/euoplocephalus_info</item>
        <item>@string/hylaeosaurus_info</item>
        <item>@string/minmi_info</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="about">This app displays a list of armored dinosaurs with their picture and their name.
                            Clicking on one dinosaur will display a detailed information on that dinosaur.
                            Created by Lyrene Labor.</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="aboutTitle">About</string>
</resources>
